Charles Lee Remington Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1936-2007; Series I
  - Denmark, Harold A. Est. number items = 11-20., 1956-1960; 000339
  - Denny, Richard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000341
  - Dethier, Vincent G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1963; 000342
  - Deutsch, Barbara. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 000343
  - Dexter, Ralph W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000346
  - Diakonoff, A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1948-1970; 000347
  - Dickinson, Mark Wade. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000348
  - Dickson, C. C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1966; 000349
  - Diehl, Edward. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1958; 000350
  - Dieke, G. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943; 000351
  - Dietrich, Henry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1949; 000352
  - Dietz, Robert A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1953; 000353
  - Dingman, V. Z. "Janie". Est. number items = 1-10., 1975-1991; 000354
  - Dirig, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1978; 000355
  - Dluthy, Eugene. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1955; 000356
  - Dobzhansky, Theodozius. Est. number items = 21-50., 1950-1971; 000357
  - Dodge, Douglas S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982-1992; 000358
  - Dodge, Harold R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000359
  - Dodson, Edward O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000360
  - Doering, Katheen C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1944; 000361
  - Dohrn, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000362
  - Dominick, Richard B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1974; 000363
  - Donahue, Julian P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1972; 000364
  - Dornfeld, Ernest J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1971; 000365
  - Douglas, Athol M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1960; 000367
  - Dowdeswell, W. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1962; 000368
  - Downes, Elizabeth F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000369
  - Downey, Duke. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000370
  - Downey, John C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1959-1973; 000371
  - Downs, Wilbur G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1979-1988; 000372
  - Doyle, Kevin. Est. number items = 1-10., 1994; 000373
  - Doyle, L. F. Boker. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1986; 000374
  - Drake, Carl J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000375
  - Drake, Ellen T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000376
  - Drake, William W. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 2001; 000377
  - Drew, Leslie C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979; 000378
  - Drummond, Boyce A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989-1990; 000379
  - Dryjowicz, John J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1961; 000380
  - Duane, John P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 000382
  - Duffner, O. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1933-1938; 000383
  - Dunbar, Carl O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1959; 000385
  - Duncan, Douglas K. Est. number items = 11-20., 1933-1936; 000386
  - Dunn, Gary A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1984; 000387
  - Dunn, L. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000388
  - Dunning, Dorothy C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1964; 000389
  - Durden, Christopher J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1966; 000390
  - Durfrane, Abel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 000391
  - Dutton, Thomas. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000392
  - Dybas, Henry S. "Hank". Est. number items = 21-50., 1944-1970; 000393
  - Easterlin, W. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000394
  - Ebeling, Alfred W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1964-1989; 000395
  - Ebert, Heinz. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000396
  - Ebner, James A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963; 000397
  - Edinger, J. &. Babette. Est. number items = 1-10., 1996; 000398
  - Edmunds, George F. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000399
  - Edwards, John S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000400
  - Eff, Donald J. Est. number items = 50+., 1942-1991; 000401
  - Egler, Frank E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1978; 000402
  - Ehle, George. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1963; 000403
  - Ehrenborg, Jeanne. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943; 000404
  - Ehrlich, Paul R. Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1997; 000405
  - Eichler, Alfred J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000406
  - Eichlin, Thomas D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 000407
  - Eisner, Thomas. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-1983; 000408
  - Eliazar, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000409
  - Elischewitz, Harold. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000410
  - Elkins, Joe C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000411
  - Elliott, D. W. T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1928; 000412
  - Elliott, Richard W. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1978-1982; 000413
  - Ellis, Peggy E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1963; 000414
  - Ellis, Scott. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1974; 000415
  - Elmore, Francis H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000416
  - Ely, Charles Russell. Est. number items = 1-10., 000417
  - Emerson, Alfred E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1968; 000418
  - Emery, D. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915; 000419
  - Emmel, John F. Est. number items = 11-20., 1961-1969; 000420
  - Emmel, Thomas C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1986; 000421
  - Emsley, Michael G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000422
  - Enberg, Carl C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1920-1922; 000423
  - Enders, Robert K. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000424
  - Endler, John A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1990; 000425
  - Engelhardt, G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941-1942; 000426
  - Englert, DuWayne C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963; 000427
  - Enns, Wilbur R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941-1962; 000428
  - Epstein, Marc. Est. number items = 1-10., 1978-1982; 000429
  - Erskine, Malcom E. (Mrs. ). Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000430
  - Esaki, Teiso. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1965; 000431
  - Esch, Harald E. (Mrs. ). Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000432
  - Eshnaur, W. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 000433
  - Essig, E. O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945-1946; 000434
  - Eustis, Henry W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1944-1947; 000435
  - Eutting, Neil A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1954; 000436
  - Evans, John G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000437
  - Evans, William H. Est. number items = 50+., 1949-1974; 000438
  - Eyer, John R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1967; 000439
  - Faber, Betty L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 000440
  - Fager, Edward W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000441
  - Fales, John H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1958; 000442
  - Farish, Donald J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1965; 000443
  - Faron, Rene. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 000444
  - Farrer, W. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1922; 000445
  - Fattig, P. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943; 000446
  - Federley, Harry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1951; 000447
  - Feininger, Andreas. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1958; 000448
  - Feinleib, Mary Ella. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979; 000449
  - Fender, Kenneth M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 000450
  - Ferguson, Douglas C. Est. number items = 50+., 1949-1974; 000451
  - Ferguson, Lynn M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979; 000452
  - Ferguson, Sybil B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000453
  - Fernald, M. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000454
  - Ferris, Clifford D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1971; 000455
  - Ferriss, Jas H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1922; 000456
  - Feyling, Paul A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1963; 000457
  - Field, William D. Est. number items = 11-20., 1948-1957; 000458
  - Figg-Hoblyn, John P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1956; 000459
  - Finch, S. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 000460
  - Fischer, T. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000461
  - Fisher, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000462
  - Fisk, Frank W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1956-1977; 000463
  - Fitch, Richard J. Est. number items = 11-20., 1944-1956; 000464
  - Fleming, Maud. Est. number items = 1-10., 1938; 000465
  - Foerster, Juan. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1954; 000466
  - Folkerts, George W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 000467
  - Fooden, Jack. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000468
  - Forbes, William T. M. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1957; 000469
  - Ford, E. B. "Henry". Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1981; 000470
  - Forster, Walter. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1960; 000471
  - Forsyth, Adrian. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000472
  - Forsyth, Marguerite S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000473
  - Foster, Kendall. Est. number items = 1-10., 1916-1917; 000474
  - Fowell, Ruth G. N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000475
  - Fowler, D. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000476
  - Fox, Richard M. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1964; 000477
  - Franclemont, John G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1952-1960; 000478
  - Franz, J. M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 000479
  - Frazer, J. F. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000480
  - Frazier, Margaret A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000481
  - Frechin, Don. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1969; 000482
  - Frederick, Albert C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000483
  - Freeman, B. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000484
  - Freeman, H. Avery. Est. number items = 21-50., 1947-1973; 000485
  - Freeman, John Levorsen. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1982; 000486
  - Freeman, Thomas N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1968; 000487
  - Freund, Rudolf. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965-1969; 000488
  - Friday, F. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1935-1937; 000489
  - Friedlander, Timothy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 000490
  - Friend, Roger B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1956; 000491
  - Frische, Carl A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000492
  - Frizzell, Harriet (Don L. ). Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1988; 000493
  - Froeschner, Richard C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1967; 000494
  - Frommer, Saul. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000495
  - Frost, C. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1914; 000496
  - Frost, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000497
  - Frost, Stuart W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1949; 000498
  - Frydenberg, Ove. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000499
  - Fuller, Stanley V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1962; 000500
  - Funkenhouser, W. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1944; 000501
  - Furth, David G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-2005; 000502
  - Gaige, Frederick M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1932; 000503
  - Gaillard, F. Harry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000504
  - Galindo, Pedro. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000505
  - Gall, Joseph G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000506
  - Gardiner, Brian O. C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1961-1962; 000507
  - Gardner, Dana L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000508
  - Gardner, James E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000509
  - Gardner, Richard C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 000510
  - Gardner, Warren F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1992; 000511
  - Garman, Philip. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000512
  - Garratt, George A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1953; 000513
  - Garrison, Barrett. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000514
  - Gastel, Barbara. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982-1984; 000515
  - Gaston, Anthony J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1975; 000516
  - Gehring, Walter J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985; 000517
  - Geis, Joe H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000518
  - George, B. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000519
  - Gerhard, William J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 000520
  - Gerould, John H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1945-1955; 000521
  - Gertsch, Willis J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1964; 000522
  - Gifffen, Judith. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 000523
  - Gijzen, Agatha. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000524
  - Gilbert, Larry E. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-2000; 000525
  - Gilbert, Pamela. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000526
  - Gilchrist, George W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 000527
  - Giles, Norman H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000528
  - Gill, Frank B. Est. number items = 11-20., 1973-1978; 000529
  - Gill, Geoffrey. Est. number items = 1-10., 1944-1946; 000530
  - Gillette, Clyde F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1985; 000531
  - Gillham, Bert A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1927; 000532
  - Gillham, Nicholas W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1952-1975; 000533
  - Ginevan, Michael E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000534
  - Glance, Grace. Est. number items = 11-20., 1947-1949; 000535
  - Glanz, Aminadov. Est. number items = 1-10., 000536
  - Glanz, Elliot. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000537
  - Glass, Bentley. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000538
  - Glass, W. Everett. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1981; 000539
  - Glazbrook, H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1936-1937; 000540
  - Glennie, E. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1948; 000541
  - Godwin, Paul Albert "Bert". Est. number items = 1-10., 1983-1986; 000542
  - Goldman, Michael A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 000543
  - Goldstein, Edward L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1978; 000544
  - Goodnight, Clarence J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1948; 000545
  - Goodpasture, Carll. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000546
  - Goodrich, Calvin. Est. number items = 21-50., 1924-1932; 000547
  - Goodrich, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1992-1994; 000548
  - Goodwin, Richard H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1987; 000549
  - Goosey, John W. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000550
  - Gordh, Gordon. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000551
  - Gordon, Malcolm S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000552
  - Gordon, William M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1940; 000553
  - Gorelick, Glenn A. Est. number items = 1-10., 000554
  - Gosline, William A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1950; 000555
  - Gottschalk, Carl W. Est. number items = 1-10., 000556
  - Gozmany, Lancelot A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1914-1965; 000557
  - Grabel, Arthur. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000558
  - Grabel, Queenie. Est. number items = 1-10., 1944; 000559
  - Grant, Harold J. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000560
  - Grant, Peter R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1980; 000561
  - Grant, Steve. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000562
  - Grant, Verne. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1979; 000563
  - Gray, Alice. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000564
  - Gray, P. H. H. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1961; 000565
  - Gray, Richard E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000566
  - Greenman, Alison J. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000567
  - Greenman, J. M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000568
  - Gregg, Clifford C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1952; 000569
  - Gregory, David P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000570
  - Greist, Darton&Dorothy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000571
  - Greist, Norman A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000572
  - Gressitt, J. Linsley. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1976; 000573
  - Grey, L. Paul. Est. number items = 50+., 1933-1982; 000574
  - Griewisch, Louis. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1955; 000575
  - Griffin, Donald R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000576
  - Griffiths, F. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000577
  - Grigione, Melissa. Est. number items = 1-10., 1991-2000; 000578
  - Grimaldi, David. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000579
  - Grimshawe, Florence M. Est. number items = 21-50., 1945-1958; 000580
  - Griswold, A. Whitney. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1959; 000581
  - Grocoff, Marc W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1978; 000582
  - Gruen, Elmer. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000583
  - Gulotta, Leroy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1948; 000584
  - Gunderson, Trygve. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000585
  - Guppy, Richard W. Est. number items = 50+., 1950-1987; 000586
  - Gurney, Ashley B. Est. number items = 11-20., 1941-1967; 000587
  - Gustafson, J. F. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1948; 000588
  - Hackman, Walter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1958; 000589
  - Hagen, Donald. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1968; 000590
  - Hall, E. Raymond. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000591
  - Hall, Ralph C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 000592
  - Hammer, William A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1938-1959; 000593
  - Hammond, H. E. Est. number items = 21-50., 1959-1963; 000594
  - Hand, E. E. Est. number items = 11-20., 1914-1926; 000595
  - Hansen, H. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1963; 000596
  - Happ, George B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1964; 000597
  - Harbison, Charles F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1965; 000598
  - Harcourt, Edith W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1937; 000599
  - Hardy, D. Elmo. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1960; 000600
  - Hargreaves, J. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923-1924; 000601
  - Harper, A. T. Est. number items = 11-20., 1936-1938; 000602
  - Harris, Edward J. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1962; 000603
  - Harris, Lucien Jr. Est. number items = 50+., 1936-1971; 000604
  - Hartman, Willard D. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-2004; 000605
  - Haskin, Caryl P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1980; 000606
  - Hata, Yoshihiko. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000607
  - Hatch, Melville H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1949; 000608
  - Hathaway, Mary. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977-1984; 000609
  - Hawks, David C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000610
  - Hawksley, "Oz". Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1996; 000611
  - Hawksworth, F. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1961; 000612
  - Hayes, Joseph B. Est. number items = 21-50., 1955-1965; 000613
  - Hayward, Kenneth J. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1963; 000614
  - Heath, John. Est. number items = 11-20., 1958-1974; 000615
  - Heineman, Bernard. Est. number items = 21-50., 1954-1969; 000616
  - Heinrich, Bernd. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1974; 000617
  - Heinrich, Gerd H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1963; 000618
  - Heitzman, J. Richard. Est. number items = 21-50., 1959-1986; 000619
  - Hemming, Frances. Est. number items = 21-50., 1948-1957; 000620
  - Henderson, David J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976; 000621
  - Henne, Christopher. Est. number items = 21-50., 1937-1970; 000622
  - Henson, W. R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1991; 000623
  - Herlan, Peter J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1969; 000624
  - Heron, R. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 000625
  - Herrera, Jose. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1956; 000626
  - Hessel, John H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 000627
  - Hessel, Sidney A. Est. number items = 50+., 1950-1962; 000628
  - Hessel, Susan. Est. number items = 1-10., 000629
  - Higginbottom, Edric. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000630
  - Hill, Charles A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1960-1966; 000631
  - Hill, Howard R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923-1925; 000632
  - Hill, Ray J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000633
  - Hilton, W. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000634
  - Hinkley, A. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915-1920; 000635
  - Hinton, Claude W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1958; 000636
  - Hinton, Howard E. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1971; 000637
  - Hlavac, T. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975; 000638
  - Hobbs, Edmund Everett Sr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923-1928; 000639
  - Hobbs, Kenneth R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000640
  - Hocking, B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000641
  - Hodge, Charles. Est. number items = 1-10., 000642
  - Hoff, C. Clayton. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1958; 000643
  - Hoffman, Richard L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1973; 000644
  - Hoffmann, Richard J. Est. number items = 11-20., 1973-1975; 000645
  - Hoffmeyer, Skat. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1967; 000646
  - Holmes, David R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000647
  - Honeybourne, T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1960; 000648
  - Hoogstraal, Harry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945-1949; 000649
  - Hooper, Ronald R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1969; 000650
  - Hooper, Ted. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1961; 000651
  - Hopf, Alice L. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1961; 000652
  - Hopfinger, John C. Est. number items = 50+., 1916-1962; 000653
  - Hopkins, G. H. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1940-1948; 000654
  - Houtz, William H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000655
  - Hovanitz, William. Est. number items = 21-50., 1937-1962; 000656
  - Howarth, T. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1959; 000657
  - Howden, Henry F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1986; 000658
  - Howe, William H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1964; 000659
  - Howell, John Thomas. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000660
  - Hrubant, H. Everett. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000661
  - Hubbell, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1992; 000662
  - Hubbell, Stephen P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1962; 000663
  - Hubbell, Theodore H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1966; 000664
  - Huber, Ronald L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1998; 000665
  - Hukusima, Syozo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000666
  - Hull, Frank M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1958; 000667
  - Hunter, George W., III. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000668
  - Hutchings, Gord H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000669
  - Hutchinson, G. Evelyn. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1958; 000670
  - Huteliwson, Francis & Joyce. Est. number items = 1-10., 1991; 000671
  - Ide, F. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1964; 000672
  - Innoue, Hiroshi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1964; 000673
  - Irland, Llyod C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985; 000674
  - Irwin, Roderick R. Est. number items = 11-20., 1969-1987; 000675
  - Isla, Ricardo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000676
  - Iwase, Taro. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1953; 000677
  - Jackson, Ralph W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1923-1927; 000678
  - Jackson, T. H. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1960; 000679
  - Jacobi, E. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000680
  - Jacobs, Leo E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1958; 000681
  - Janetschek, Heinz. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1961; 000682
  - Jefferson, R. N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000683
  - Jewett, Stanley G. Jr. Est. number items = 21-50., 1954-1984; 000684
  - John, Bernard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000685
  - Johns, Doris. Est. number items = 1-10., 1939; 000686
  - Johnson, Charles W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1922-1931; 000687
  - Johnson, Harry L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1955; 000688
  - Johnson, John C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1971; 000689
  - Johnson, Kurt. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1999; 000690
  - Johnson, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1991; 000691
  - Jolly, Alison. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982-1996; 000692
  - Jones, Ben. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1979; 000693
  - Jones, Frank Morton. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1959; 000694
  - Jones, Walter B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000695
  - Jordanof, Mary Jopdan Chr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000696
  - Judd, W. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1970; 000697
  - Jumalon, Julian N. Est. number items = 11-20., 1958-1973; 000698
  - Kaisila, Jouko. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1958; 000699
  - Kamp, William J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963; 000700
  - Kaneshiro, Ken. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000701
  - Kara, Charles J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1998-1999; 000702
  - Karalus, Karl E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956-1957; 000703
  - Katson, B. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945-1955; 000704
  - Katz, Jay. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970-1972; 000705
  - Kaufeldt, Carlos E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000706
  - Kazakova, Irina. Est. number items = 1-10., 1992-1995; 000707
  - Keast, Allen. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1954; 000708
  - Keegan, Hugh L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1947-1948; 000709
  - Kendall, Roy O. Est. number items = 50+., 1957-1990; 000710
  - Kennedy, Clarence K. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 000711
  - Kesselring, Jorge. Est. number items = 50+., 1950-1968; 000712
  - Kettlewell, H. Bernard D. Est. number items = 21-50., 1955-1970; 000713